track-trace.com 2011-01-06

# Privacy statement - track-trace

**Information Collection and Use**

Webfokus is the sole owner of the information collected on this site. We will not sell, share, or rent this information to others in ways different from what is disclosed in this statement. Webfokus collects information from our users at several different points on this website.

**Cookies**

A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Usage of a cookie is in no way linked to any personally identifiable information while on our site. Cookies are used to store information entered by the users so that they do not have to reenter this information on their next visit. Cookies can be disabled in most browsers preferences. If a user rejects the cookie our site may still be used, the drawback to this is that the user will have to retype information on every visit to our site.

**Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit our website. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address, or telephone number) about your visits to this and other websites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services of interest to you. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this information used by these companies, read the privacy policies of [Google](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html), [ContextWeb](http://www.contextweb.com/ppolicy.html), [ValueClick Media](http://valueclickmedia.com/webuser_privacy.shtml) and [Redux media](http://www.reduxmedia.com/comp_privacy.htm).

**Log files**

We use IP addresses to analyse trends, administer the site, track user movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information.

**Links**

This web site contains links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. We encourage our users to be aware when they leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every web site that collects personally identifiable information. This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by this Web site.

**Feedback**

If users elects to use our feedback service for informing us of problems with our site or suggest improvements, we ask them for their email address. We will only use this information to respond to the entered topic, and the user will never receive emails from us that are not related to this. The user may choose not to enter their email address, the drawback to this is that we will not be able to respond to the users request.

**Tell A Friend**

If a user elects to use our referral service for informing a friend about our site, we ask them for the users name and the friend's email address. We will automatically send the friend a email inviting her to visit the site. The entered information will be used for the sole purpose of sending this email and the receiver will never receive emails from us that are not related to this.

**Notification of changes**

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on our Homepage so our users are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under which circumstances, if any, we disclose it. If at any point we decide to use personally identifiable information in a manner different from that stated at the time it was collected, we will notify users by way of an email. Users will have a choice as to whether or not we use their information in this different manner. We will use information in accordance with the privacy policy under which the information was collected.

**Contacting the Web Site**

If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site, you can contact us through our contact page.
